Records, 1972-1984 related records, 1971-1978
Smithsonian Institution Archives
- OFFICE OF THE UNDER SECRETARY, RECORDS, 1980-1981., Series 4
  - Box 14
    - Stuart Portraits (1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Symposia and Seminars (Box 14 of 23)
    - T (miscellaneous) (1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Time Machine (1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Telecommunications (1981/1980/1979) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Television Committee (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Cable Television Report-Cherkezian (1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Treasurer's Office (1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Visitor Information and Associates Reception Center (1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Wharton Summer Intern Program (1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - White House (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Wilson Center (1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Women's Council (1981-1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Wolf, Tom-TV consultant (1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Zoo (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
- OFFICE OF THE UNDER SECRETARY, RECORDS, 1980-1983., Series 5
  - Box 15
    - 1982 Files
    - A (Box 15 of 23)
    - Administration (Box 15 of 23)
    - Anacostia Neighborhood Museum (Box 15 of 23)
    - Archeometry (Box 15 of 23)
    - Associates - Resident (Box 15 of 23)
    - Arts Industries Bldg. (Box 15 of 23)
    - Archives (Box 15 of 23)
    - Audiovisual (Box 15 of 23)
    - Audits (Box 15 of 23)
    - Awards (Box 15 of 23)
    - B (Box 15 of 23)
    - Belmont (Box 15 of 23)
    - George Brakeley (Fundraiser for Quadrangle) (Box 15 of 23)
    - Budget: Self-assessment project (1982 and 1981) (Box 15 of 23)
    - Brooks Award (Box 15 of 23)
    - C (Box 15 of 23)
    - Mark Cannon (Box 15 of 23)
    - Chron (1982, 1981 and 1980) (Box 15 of 23)
    - Club of Rome (Box 15 of 23)
    - Cold storage for photographic material (Box 15 of 23)
    - Collections acquisition, scholarly studies educational outreach program (Box 15 of 23)
    - Collections management (Box 15 of 23)
    - Conservation Analytical Laboratory (Box 15 of 23)
    - Contingency plans: absence of appropriations (Box 15 of 23)
    - Contracts (Box 15 of 23)
    - Division of Performing Arts (Box 15 of 23)
    - Egyptian Minister of Culture Visit (Box 15 of 23)
    - Equal opportunity (Box 15 of 23)
    - Executive Resources Board (Box 15 of 23)
    - Exhibit (Box 15 of 23)
    - Fellowships and Grants (Box 15 of 23)
    - Folklife Programs (Box 15 of 23)
    - G (Box 15 of 23)
    - General Counsel (Box 15 of 23)
    - General Services Administration (Box 15 of 23)
    - Hirshhorn Museum (Box 15 of 23)
    - Information Resource Management (Box 15 of 23)
    - International Exchange Service (Box 15 of 23)
    - Internships (Box 15 of 23)
    - J (Box 15 of 23)
    - L (Box 15 of 23)
    - Libraries (Box 15 of 23)
    - Library Review Committee, 1981 (Box 15 of 23)
    - M (Box 15 of 23)
    - Management Analysis Office (Box 15 of 23)
    - Membership and Development (Box 15 of 23)
    - Museum of Man (Box 15 of 23)
    - Museum Support Center (Box 15 of 23)
    - Museum Support Center; space problems and move (Box 15 of 23)
  - Box 16
    - Macarthur Foundation (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Air and Space Museum (NASM) (Box 16 of 23)
    - NASM-Congressman Dellums (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Museum of African Art (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Museum of American Art (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Museum of American History (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Museum of Natural History (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Portrait Gallery (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Human Studies Film Center (Box 16 of 23)
    - National Human Studies Film Center Advisory Council (Box 16 of 23)
    - Ocean Project (Box 16 of 23)
    - Office of Management and Budget (Box 16 of 23)
    - Parking (employee) 1980-1982 (Box 16 of 23)
    - Paul Perrot (Box 16 of 23)
    - Personnel (Box 16 of 23)
    - Personnel: Applicants (Box 16 of 23)
    - Personnel: Merit pay (Box 16 of 23)
    - Personnel: Excomm performance appraisals (Box 16 of 23)
    - Protection (Box 16 of 23)
    - Public Service (Box 16 of 23)
    - Public Service reorganization (Box 16 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Publishing Council (Box 16 of 23)
    - Quadrangle (Box 16 of 23)
    - R (Box 16 of 23)
    - Radiation Biology Laboratory (Box 16 of 23)
    - Reading Is Fundamental (Box 16 of 23)
    - Regents: Mr. Humelsine (Box 16 of 23)
    - Regents: Senator Jackson (Box 16 of 23)
    - Regents: Mr. Webb (Box 16 of 23)
    - Registrar (Box 16 of 23)
    - Research awards program (Box 16 of 23)
    - S. Dillon Ripley, 1980-1982 (Box 16 of 23)
    - S (Box 16 of 23)
    - SITES (Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service) (Box 16 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (Box 16 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Conference (Box 16 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Council (Box 16 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Traveling Exhibition Service (Box 16 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Magazine (Box 16 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Press (Box 16 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Tropical Research Institute (Box 16 of 23)
  - Box 17
    - Smithsonian World (Box 17 of 23)
    - Smithsonian World-1983 (Box 17 of 23)
    - Space problems (Box 17 of 23)
    - Special Events (Box 17 of 23)
    - Strike response plan (contingency) (Box 17 of 23)
    - Summer hours (Box 17 of 23)
    - Symposia and Seminars (Box 17 of 23)
    - T (Box 17 of 23)
    - Telecommunications (Box 17 of 23)
    - Treasurer (Box 17 of 23)
    - Visitor Information and Reception Center (Box 17 of 23)
    - Webb Fellowships (established 1982) (Box 17 of 23)
    - White House (Box 17 of 23)
    - Williamsburg (Box 17 of 23)
    - Wolf, Tom (research report; video education resource series for high schools) (Box 17 of 23)
    - Congressman Yates (Box 17 of 23)
    - Yorktown (1981-1982) (Box 17 of 23)
    - Zoo (Box 17 of 23)
    - Zoo-deer at Front Royal (1982-1983) (Box 17 of 23)
    - 1983 Files
    - Collection Management 1983 (Box 17 of 23)
    - Statement by Under Secretary and exhibits on collection management prepared for appropriation hearings, April 1983 (Box 17 of 23)
    - James E. Webb Fellowship (Box 17 of 23)
- OFFICE OF THE UNDER SECRETARY, RECORDS, 1980-1984., Series 6
  - Box 18
    - A (Box 18 of 23)
    - Walter Adey (Box 18 of 23)
    - Walter Adey (1980-1982) (Box 18 of 23)
    - Advertising: Office Memorandum (1981) (Box 18 of 23)
    - Administration (Box 18 of 23)
    - Archives (Box 18 of 23)
    - Arts and Industries Building (Box 18 of 23)
    - Associates: Resident (Box 18 of 23)
    - Associates: National (Box 18 of 23)
    - Audits (Box 18 of 23)
    - Awards (Box 18 of 23)
    - Edward Ayensu (Box 18 of 23)
    - B (Box 18 of 23)
    - Brooks Award (Box 18 of 23)
    - C (Box 18 of 23)
    - Chesapeake Bay Center (Box 18 of 23)
    - Chron (1983) (Box 18 of 23)
    - Collaborative Education Program (Box 18 of 23)
    - Commission of Fine Arts (1980-1983) (Box 18 of 23)
    - Congress (Box 18 of 23)
    - Contingency Plan: Absence of Appropriations (Box 18 of 23)
    - Council of Bureau Directors (Box 18 of 23)
    - Division of Performing Arts Reorganization (Box 18 of 23)
    - Edinburgh Festival (1983-1984) (Box 18 of 23)
    - Department of Energy (Box 18 of 23)
    - Equal Opportunity (Box 18 of 23)
    - Executive Resources Board (Box 18 of 23)
    - Exhibits (Box 18 of 23)
    - Fellowships and Grants (Box 18 of 23)
    - Five-Year Prospectus (Box 18 of 23)
    - Folklife Programs (Box 18 of 23)
    - Food Service (Box 18 of 23)
    - Freer Gallery of Art (Box 18 of 23)
    - General Accounting Office (Box 18 of 23)
    - General Counsel (Box 18 of 23)
    - German Map (Box 18 of 23)
    - H (Box 18 of 23)
    - Heye Foundation (1980-1981) (Box 18 of 23)
    - Hirshhorn (Box 18 of 23)
    - Horticulture (Box 18 of 23)
    - Holy Land Exhibit (Box 18 of 23)
    - Information Resource Management (Box 18 of 23)
    - Internal Controls Steering Committee (Box 18 of 23)
    - International Exchange Service (Box 18 of 23)
    - Internships (Box 18 of 23)
    - K (Box 18 of 23)
    - Libraries (Box 18 of 23)
    - M (Box 18 of 23)
    - Mail Order Division (Box 18 of 23)
    - Management Analysis Office (Box 18 of 23)
    - Membership and Development (Box 18 of 23)
    - Museum Support Center (Box 18 of 23)
  - Box 19
    - N (Box 19 of 23)
    - National Air and Space Museum (Box 19 of 23)
    - National Human Studies Film Center (Box 19 of 23)
    - National Museum of African Art (Box 19 of 23)
    - National Museum of American Art (Box 19 of 23)
    - National Museum of American History (Box 19 of 23)
    - National Museum of Natural History (NMNH) (Box 19 of 23)
    - NMNH: Gems and Minerals (Box 19 of 23)
    - NMNH: Gems and Minerals (1981-1982) (Box 19 of 23)
    - NMNH: Gems and Minerals materials for hearings 4-15-85 (Box 19 of 23)
    - National Portrait Gallery (Box 19 of 23)
    - Native American Indians (1981-1983) (Box 19 of 23)
    - Office of Management and Budget (Box 19 of 23)
    - OPlants (Box 19 of 23)
    - Parking (Box 19 of 23)
    - Parking (Mall) (Box 19 of 23)
    - Paul Perrot (Box 19 of 23)
    - Personnel (Box 19 of 23)
    - Personnel: Applicants (Box 19 of 23)
    - Personnel: Merit pay (Box 19 of 23)
    - Personnel: Excomm performance appraisals (Box 19 of 23)
    - Personnel: Excomm performance plans (Box 19 of 23)
    - Protection (Box 19 of 23)
    - Public Affairs (Box 19 of 23)
    - Public Service (Box 19 of 23)
    - Publishing Council (Box 19 of 23)
    - Mr. Hughes' Appointment Books (1980-1983) (Box 19 of 23)
  - Box 20
    - Quadrangle (Box 20 of 23)
    - Quadrangle construction project (Box 20 of 23)
    - Quadrangle: International Center, Islamic Studies Center (Box 20 of 23)
    - R (Box 20 of 23)
    - Regents: (Box 20 of 23)
      Mr. Acheson (1982)
      Mr. Austin
      Mr. Bowen (1980-83)
      Sen. Goldwater (1982)
      Judge Higginbotham (1982)
      Mr. Humelsine
    - Registrar (Box 20 of 23)
    - Renaming of museums-NMAH (National Museum of American History) NMAA (National Museum of American Art) (1980) (Box 20 of 23)
    - Research Institute for Immigration and Ethnic Studies (Box 20 of 23)
    - S (Box 20 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (Box 20 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Council (Box 20 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Magazine (Box 20 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Press (Box 20 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Traveling Exhibition Service (Box 20 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Tropical Research Institute (Box 20 of 23)
    - Smithsonian World (1984) (Box 20 of 23)
    - Smithsonian World costs incurred (1983-1984) (Box 20 of 23)
    - Space problems (Box 20 of 23)
    - Speeches and remarks (1980-1984) (Box 20 of 23)
    - Symposia And Seminars (Box 20 of 23)
    - Tariff Building (1982-1983) (Box 20 of 23)
    - Larry Taylor (1983-1984) (Box 20 of 23)
    - Telecommunications (Box 20 of 23)
    - Treasurer (recruitment for) (1984) (Box 20 of 23)
    - Truman Centennial, May 4, 1984 (1983-1984) (Box 20 of 23)
    - UNESCO conference (1984) (Box 20 of 23)
    - Visitor Information and Reception Center (Box 20 of 23)
    - W (Box 20 of 23)
    - Wilson Center (Box 20 of 23)
    - World Wildlife Fund (Box 20 of 23)
    - Women's Council (Box 20 of 23)
    - Barry Yampol (Research Charitable Trust) gems (Box 20 of 23)
    - Zoo, 1983 (Box 20 of 23)
- OFFICE OF THE UNDER SECRETARY, RECORDS, 1983-1984., Series 7
  - Box 21
    - A (Box 21 of 23)
    - Mr. Adams (Box 21 of 23)
    - Administration (Box 21 of 23)
    - American Consortium for International Public Administration (Box 21 of 23)
    - Anacostia Neighborhood Museum (Box 21 of 23)
    - Archives of American Art (Box 21 of 23)
    - Arts Industries Building (Box 21 of 23)
    - Associates: National (Box 21 of 23)
    - Associates: Resident (Box 21 of 23)
    - Associates/Performing Arts (NMAH) (Box 21 of 23)
    - Audits (Box 21 of 23)
    - Audiovisual programs (Box 21 of 23)
    - Awards (Box 21 of 23)
    - Brooks Award (Box 21 of 23)
    - Budget priorities-FY 1986 properties (Box 21 of 23)
    - Budget review process (Box 21 of 23)
    - Census Bureau (Box 21 of 23)
    - Chief Justice of the Supreme Court (Box 21 of 23)
    - Chron (1984) (Box 21 of 23)
    - Collections Management (Box 21 of 23)
    - Committee for a Wider Audience (Box 21 of 23)
    - Congress-Subcommittee on Public Buildings re: science facilities (Box 21 of 23)
    - Construction-Mr. Hughes Acting (Box 21 of 23)
    - Contingency plan: absence of appropriations (Box 21 of 23)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Museum (Box 21 of 23)
    - Directorate of International Activities (Box 21 of 23)
    - EarthWatch (Box 21 of 23)
    - Equal Opportunity (Box 21 of 23)
    - Evans Gallery (NMNH) (Box 21 of 23)
    - Executive Resources Board (Box 21 of 23)
    - Exhibits (Box 21 of 23)
    - Fellowships and Grants (Box 21 of 23)
    - Folklife Programs (Box 21 of 23)
    - Food Service (Box 21 of 23)
    - Freer Gallery of Art (Box 21 of 23)
    - General Accounting Office (Box 21 of 23)
    - General Counsel (Box 21 of 23)
    - Hirshhorn (Box 21 of 23)
    - Holocaust (Box 21 of 23)
    - Horticulture (Box 21 of 23)
  - Box 22
    - Information Resource Management (Box 22 of 23)
    - Institute of Museum Services (Box 22 of 23)
    - Internal controls (Box 22 of 23)
    - International Activities (Box 22 of 23)
    - Internships (Box 22 of 23)
    - Israeli exhibit (Box 22 of 23)
    - K (Box 22 of 23)
    - Kellogg Project (Box 22 of 23)
    - Kennedy Center (Box 22 of 23)
    - Libraries (Box 22 of 23)
    - Living Presidents (Box 22 of 23)
    - M (Box 22 of 23)
    - Membership and Development (Box 22 of 23)
    - Mosque model (Box 22 of 23)
    - Museum Programs (Box 22 of 23)
    - Museum Support Center (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Air and Space Museum (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Armed Forces Advisory Board (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Geographic Society (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Human Studies Film Center (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Museum of African Art (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Museum of American Art (Box 22 of 23)
    - NMAA: closing of 8th Street (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Museum of American History (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Museum of Natural History (Box 22 of 23)
    - NMNH: Gems and minerals (Box 22 of 23)
    - National Portrait Gallery (Box 22 of 23)
    - Native American Indians (Box 22 of 23)
    - Old Post Office Building (Box 22 of 23)
    - Office of Management and Budget (Box 22 of 23)
    - Parking (Box 22 of 23)
    - Payroll personnel system (Box 22 of 23)
    - Personnel (Box 22 of 23)
    - Personnel: Applicants (Box 22 of 23)
    - Personnel: Assistant Secretary for Museums (Box 22 of 23)
    - Personnel: Grievances (Box 22 of 23)
    - Personnel: Merit pay (Box 22 of 23)
    - Personnel: Excomm performance appraisals (Box 22 of 23)
  - Box 23
    - Precious Legacy (exhibit) (Box 23 of 23)
    - Presidential inauguration (Box 23 of 23)
    - Protection (Box 23 of 23)
    - Public Relations (Box 23 of 23)
    - Public Affairs (Box 23 of 23)
    - Public Service (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle Education Center (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle film (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle garden (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle Information Center (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle International Center (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle International Center, Fulbright Fellowship (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle Islamic Studies Center (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle library (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle Sackler Gallery (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle: SITES (Box 23 of 23)
    - Quadrangle: Wilson Center (Box 23 of 23)
    - Board of Regents (miscellaneous) (1980-1984) (Box 23 of 23)
    - Regents Audit and Review Committee (Box 23 of 23)
    - Regents: (Box 23 of 23)
      Chief Justice (1983)
      Dr. Bowen
      Mrs. Clark (1983-1984)
    - Research (Box 23 of 23)
    - Roosevelt (Eleanor) Centennial (Box 23 of 23)
    - S (Box 23 of 23)
    - Dr. Sackler (Box 23 of 23)
    - Dr. Sackler-Henderson Island (Box 23 of 23)
    - SITES (Land and buildings) 1983-84 (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Council (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Environmental Research Center (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Magazine (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Press (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Traveling Exhibition Service (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Tropical Research Institute (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian World (Box 23 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Year (Box 23 of 23)
    - Space problems (Box 23 of 23)
    - Special Exhibition Fund (Box 23 of 23)
    - Telecommunications (Box 23 of 23)
    - Treasurer's Office (Box 23 of 23)
    - Vatican (Box 23 of 23)
    - VIPs (Box 23 of 23)
    - Visitor Information and Associates Reception Center (Box 23 of 23)
    - Webb Fellowships (Box 23 of 23)
    - Wilson Center (Box 23 of 23)
    - Zoo-deer at Front Royal (1982-1983) (Box 23 of 23)
    - Mr. Hughes' Appointment Book (1984) (Box 23 of 23)